Guide to the David Wojnarowicz Papers ca. 1954-1992 MSS.092
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VI: Biographical, 150272
  - Subseries C: Reviews, 150332
    - Review-Waterfront Journals, undated; 150337 (Box 10, Folder 77)
    - Review-Waterfront Journals, undated; 150336 (Box 10, Folder 77A.)
    - Review --- "Brush Fires in the Social Landscape", undated; 150335 (Box 10, Folder 77B.)
    - Review --- "Brush Fires in the Social Landscape", undated; 150334 (Box 10, Folder 77C.)
  - Subseries D: Business and Promotional, 150300
    - Anna Friebe Galerie invoice, undated; 150331 (Box 10, Folder 78)
    - Artist file: Anna Friebe Gallery, undated; 150330 (Box 10, Folder 78A.)
    - Artist file: Wojnarowicz bios, undated; 150329 (Box 10, Folder 78B.)
    - Artist file: Wojnarowicz exhibition flyers, undated; 150328 (Box 10, Folder 78C.)
    - Artist file: Wojnarowicz exhibition and performance flyers, undated; 150327 (Box 10, Folder 78D.)
    - Artist file: various artist-related, undated; 150326 (Box 10, Folder 78E.)
    - Bills, undated; 150325 (Box 10, Folder 79)
    - Christmas catalog and misc. Receipts, undated; 150324 (Box 10, Folder 80)
    - Close to the Knives playbill, undated; 150323 (Box 10, Folder 81)
    - Contemporary Museum Hawaii fax, undated; 150322 (Box 10, Folder 82)
    - C. W. Graphics: contract, undated; 150321 (Box 10, Folder 82A.)
    - Film rights option, undated; 150320 (Box 10, Folder 83)
    - Pollock-Krasner Foundation application, undated; 150319 (Box 10, Folder 83A.)
    - Galerie MichPle Chomette, undated; 150318 (Box 10, Folder 84)
    - Gracie Mansion Gallery, undated; 150317 (Box 10, Folder 85)
    - Gracie Mansion Gallery, etc., undated; 150316 (Box 10, Folder 86)
    - Insurance cancellation/levy sale, undated; 150315 (Box 10, Folder 87)
    - New Museum, undated; 150314 (Box 10, Folder 88)
    - Plane tickets, undated; 150313 (Box 10, Folder 89)
    - Public Art Fund Inc.: memo, undated; 150312 (Box 10, Folder 89A.)
    - Receipts 1989, 150311 (Box 10, Folder 90)
    - Receipts 1989, 150310 (Box 10, Folder 91)
    - Receipts, etc., undated; 150309 (Box 10, Folder 92)
    - Receipts, etc., undated; 150308 (Box 10, Folder 93)
    - Receipts, etc. --Spain, undated; 150307 (Box 10, Folder 94)
    - Receipts for taxes 1990-97, 1990-1997; 150306 (Box 10, Folder 95)
    - Spain gallery papers, undated; 150305 (Box 10, Folder 96)
    - Walker Art Center-Ben Neil & David Wojnarowicz/ITSOFOMO, undated; 150304 (Box 10, Folder 97)
    - Other artists' exhibition flyers and catalogs, undated; 150303 (Box 10, Folder 97A.)
    - Business cards and phone numbers, undated; 150302 (Box 10, Folder 97B.)
  - Subseries E: Taxes, Receipts, and Legal Documents, 150273
    - Receipts 1983, 150299 (Box 11, Folder 98)
    - Receipts 1983-84, 1983-1984; 150298 (Box 11, Folder 99)
    - Receipts 1984, 150297 (Box 11, Folder 100)
    - Receipts 1984, 150296 (Box 11, Folder 101)
    - Receipts 1984, 150295 (Box 11, Folder 102)
    - Receipts 1984, 150294 (Box 11, Folder 103)
    - Receipts 1985, 150293 (Box 11, Folder 104)
    - Receipts 1985, 150292 (Box 11, Folder 105)
    - Receipts 1985, 150291 (Box 11, Folder 106)
    - Receipts 1985, 150290 (Box 11, Folder 107)
    - Receipts 1985, 150289 (Box 11, Folder 108)
    - Receipts 1985, 150288 (Box 11, Folder 109)
    - Receipts 1985, 150287 (Box 11, Folder 110)
    - Receipts-art supplies, undated; 150286 (Box 11, Folder 111)
    - Receipts-bank 1986, 150285 (Box 11, Folder 112)
    - Receipts 1986, 150284 (Box 11, Folder 113)
    - Receipts 1986, 150283 (Box 12, Folder 114)
    - Receipts 1986, 150282 (Box 12, Folder 115)
    - Receipts 1986, 150281 (Box 12, Folder 116)
    - Receipts 1986, 150280 (Box 12, Folder 117)
    - Receipts 1986, 150279 (Box 12, Folder 118)
    - Receipts 1986, 150278 (Box 12, Folder 119)
    - Receipts 1986, 150277 (Box 12, Folder 120)
    - Receipts-plane tickets, undated; 150276 (Box 12, Folder 121)
    - Tax-misc., undated; 150275 (Box 12, Folder 122)
    - Tax-misc. receipts, undated; 150274 (Box 12, Folder 123)
- Series V: Art Magazines and Catalogue Contributions, 150426
  - Subseries A: Contributions of Artwork to Art Magazines by Wojnarowicz, 150498
    - Architectural Digest, undated; 150508 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Art in America July, 1988, 150507 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Artforum Summer 1993, 150506 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Artforum Sept. 1993, 150505 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Contemporary Art Contemporanea magazine November, 1990, 150504 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Horizon December, 1987, 150503 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Maandblad, undated; 150502 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - New Yorker, undated; 150501 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Spin, undated; 150500 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Subseries B: Articles by Wojnarowicz, 150491
    - Wojnarowicz "Spiral", undated; 150497 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Wojnarowicz "Being Queer in America", undated; 150496 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Wojnarowicz "Losing the Form in Darkness", undated; 150495 (Box 8, Folder 11A.)
    - Wojnarowicz with Doug Bressler "American Dreamtime", undated; 150494 (Box 8, Folder 11B.)
    - Wojnarowicz "Man in Dark Sunglasses by the Silver Arc", undated; 150493 (Box 8, Folder 11C.)
  - Subseries C: Articles on Wojnarowicz in Art Magazines, 150454
    - LD Berghtol, "In My Life," HX June, 1996, 150490 (Box 8, Folder 11E.)
    - Cindy Carr "Portrait of the Artist", undated; 150489 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Cindy Carr "Troubleshooters" Artforum September, 1990, 150488 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Lawrence Chua "David Wojnarowicz", undated; 150487 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Cone, Timothy "Art and the Law", undated; 150486 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - David Deitcher "Ideas and Emotions", undated; 150485 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - John Donahue "Flower Power", undated; 150484 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Mark Alice Durant "Sustained Rage in a Hostile Landscape", undated; 150483 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Brigitte Engler "Peinture et Guerre Civile", undated; 150482 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - David Finkle "Postcards from America", undated; 150481 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Jurgen Fischer "Neue Heimat", undated; 150480 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Nichols Fox "NEA", undated; 150479 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Stephen Hager "From Street to Salon with David.", undated; 150478 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Howard Hampton "Public Enemies" Artforum, April, 1991, 150477 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Elizabeth Hess "Queer in Normal", undated; 150476 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Joe Jarrell "God is in the Details", undated; 150475 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Koch, Stephen "Warhol", undated; 150474 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Eric Latzky "Lip Service", undated; 150473 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Lucy Lippard "Out of the Safety Zone", undated; 150472 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Carlo McCormick "High Art", undated; 150471 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - MOMA "Gathering Hope", undated; 150470 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Allan Parachini "Fighting Back", undated; 150469 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Stephen Perloff "A Censorship Diary", undated; 150468 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Sarah Pettit "The Arts", undated; 150467 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Howardena Pindella "Breaking the Silence", undated; 150466 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - . Out, Issue 1, Summer 1992, 150465 (Box 8, Folder 35 A.)
    - Calvin Reid "Beyond Mourning", undated; 150464 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Matthew Rose "David Wojnarowicz", undated; 150463 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - David Rubin "Primary Structures", undated; 150462 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Jerry Saltz "Not Going Gentle", undated; 150461 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Peter Schjeldahl "Life Equals Noise", undated; 150460 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - K. Schwartz "Continental.", undated; 150459 (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Frank Wagner "David Wojnarowicz", undated; 150458 (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - Frank Wagner "Ubers Sofa!", undated; 150457 (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - Michelle Wallace "The Cave", undated; 150456 (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - Linda Yablonskaya "Covering the Slaughterfront", undated; 150455 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Subseries D: Misc. Articles and Mentions, 150427
    [see also Flat Box]
    - David Joselit "Power of Portraitist" [on Peter Hujar], undated; 150453 (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - Frank Graziano "Alejandra Pizarnik", undated; 150452 (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - Mention-"High and Low.", undated; 150451 (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - Mention-"The Neo-Dealers", undated; 150450 (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - Mention-"Planet Ludlow", undated; 150449 (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - Mention-"Woman Behaving Badly", undated; 150448 (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - Mention --- "Rough Draft of Journal Entries from the Sur Rodney Diary" [on Keith Davis], undated; 150447 (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - Mention-"Diane Plays Ball; Katie Plays for Laughs." Premiere Magazine., undated; 150446 (Box 8, Folder 52A.)
    - Mention-"On the Waterfront" Out Magazine, 10/1997., 150445 (Box 8, Folder 52B.)
    - Mention-"A Living Testament of Blood Fairies: Part II" Art in America. 4/1997, 150444 (Box 8, Folder 52C.)
    - Mention-Art in America, 11/1994, 150443 (Box 8, Folder 53D.)
    - C. Carr, Samuel R. Delany, James A. Baggett "Born in Flames", undated; 150442 (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - Peter Walsh "Call of the Wild", undated; 150441 (Box 9, Folder 54)
    - Mention --- "Simon Says", undated; 150440 (Box 9, Folder 55)
    - Michael Kimmelman "Art Club", undated; 150439 (Box 9, Folder 56)
    - Mention --- "The Aids Decade", undated; 150438 (Box 9, Folder 57)
    - Mention --- "Mix" ("One"), undated; 150437 (Box 9, Folder 58)
    - Herbert Reichert "Life & Death", undated; 150436 (Box 9, Folder 59)
    - Bill Arning " 'Fever' Dreams", 150435 (Box 9, Folder 60)
    - Peter Von Ziegesar "(David) Wojnarowicz", undated; 150434 (Box 9, Folder 61)
    - Walter Robinson "Stray Genius", undated; 150433 (Box 9, Folder 62)
    - Mention --- Jerome Charyn, "Metropolis", undated; 150432 (Box 9, Folder 62A.)
    - Mention --- "David Wojnarowicz Feature", undated; 150431 (Box 9, Folder 63)
    - Mention --- "An Artist with a Beef", undated; 150430 (Box 9, Folder 64)
- Series VII: Subjects, 150123
  - Subseries A: Loft, 150218
    - Loft papers (1991), 150271 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Loft papers (1990), 150270 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Loft papers (1990), 150269 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Loft papers (1989), 150268 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Loft papers (1988), 150267 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Loft papers (1988), 150266 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Loft papers (1987), 150265 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Loft papers (pre-1987), 150264 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Lease (1985): 529 E. 13th St., 150263 (Box 12, Folder 8A.)
    - Loft Board files: Loft papers, Hujar 1981, 150262 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Loft papers: Hujar 1979, 150261 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Loft Board files, undated; 150260 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Loft: Raynes Realty, undated; 150259 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Misc. notes, envelopes, business cards, etc., undated; 150258 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Receipts-airline tickets, undated; 150257 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Receipts 1991, misc., 150256 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Medical receipts 1991, 150255 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Con Edison 1991, 150254 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - NY Telephone 1991, 150253 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Chemical Bank 1991, 150252 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Receipts 1990, misc., 150251 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Medical receipts 1990, 150250 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Chemical Bank 1990, 150249 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Con Edison 1990, 150248 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - NY Telephone 1990, 150247 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Receipts 1989, misc., 150246 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Medical receipts 1989, 150245 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Con Edison 1989, 150244 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - NY Telephone 1989, 150243 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Chemical Bank 1989, 150242 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Receipts 1988, misc., 150241 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Medical receipts 1988, 150240 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Manhattan Bank 1988, 150239 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Amalgamated Bank 1988, 150238 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Chemical Bank 1988, 150237 (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Con Edison 1988, 150236 (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - NY Telephone 1988, 150235 (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - Receipts-empty folders, undated; 150234 (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Tax, undated; 150233 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - Hujar, Peter-bills, undated; 150232 (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - Hujar, Peter-bills, undated; 150231 (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - Hujar, Peter-bills, undated; 150230 (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - Hujar, Peter-birth certificate, diploma, social security, etc., undated; 150229 (Box 13, Folder 42)
    - Hujar, Peter-c. v., undated; 150228 (Box 13, Folder 43)
    - Hujar, Peter-disability report, undated; 150227 (Box 13, Folder 44)
    - Hujar, Peter-home care plan, undated; 150226 (Box 13, Folder 45)
    - Hujar, Peter-medical, undated; 150225 (Box 13, Folder 46)
    - Hujar, Peter-model release forms, undated; 150224 (Box 13, Folder 47)
    - Hujar, Peter-obituary, undated; 150223 (Box 14, Folder 48)
    - Hujar, Peter-obituary, undated; 150222 (Box 14, Folder 49)
    - Hujar, Peter-obituary "Portrait in Life.", undated; 150221 (Box 14, Folder 50)
    - Hujar, Peter-receipts, undated; 150220 (Box 14, Folder 51)
    - Hujar, Peter-will, undated; 150219 (Box 14, Folder 52)
  - Subseries B: Legal Cases, 150164
    - Auto accident summons, undated; 150217 (Box 14, Folder 53)
    - Legal misc., undated; 150216 (Box 14, Folder 54)
    - Legal misc. -will of Keith Davis, undated; 150215 (Box 14, Folder 55)
    - Legal misc. -guidelines for will, undated; 150214 (Box 14, Folder 56)
    - NEA-Artists Space, undated; 150213 (Box 14, Folder 57)
    - NEA-"Culture Wars" by Ed Richard Bolton, undated; 150212 (Box 14, Folder 58)
    - NEA-"Left & Right ..." by David Levi Strauss, undated; 150211 (Box 14, Folder 59)
    - NEA-"NEA Restores $10,000 Grant ... " by Karen Lipson (NY Newsday), undated; 150210 (Box 14, Folder 60)
    - NEA-Illinois State University controversy articles/clippings, undated; 150209 (Box 14, Folder 61)
    - NEA-Illinois correspondence re: attacks on retrospective by NEA, undated; 150208 (Box 14, Folder 62)
    - NEA-Illinois correspondence re: "Tongues of Flame" exhibit, undated; 150207 (Box 14, Folder 63)
    - NEA-Ollie North file, undated; 150206 (Box 14, Folder 64)
    - NEA-Postcards from America excerpt, undated; 150205 (Box 14, Folder 65)
    - NEA-Proof (Artist's Equity) "Paint or Politics", undated; 150204 (Box 14, Folder 66)
    - NEA/AFA case-reviews, undated; 150203 (Box 14, Folder 67)
    - Wildmon-AFA fax, undated; 150202 (Box 14, Folder 68)
    - Wildmon-AFA fax, undated; 150201 (Box 14, Folder 69)
    - Wildmon-AFA flyer, undated; 150200 (Box 14, Folder 70)
    - Wildmon-AFA letter about Wojnarowicz, undated; 150199 (Box 14, Folder 71)
    - Wildmon-AFA letter requesting money, undated; 150198 (Box 14, Folder 72)
    - Wildmon-AFA memo, undated; 150197 (Box 14, Folder 73)
    - Wildmon/NEA-articles and clippings, undated; 150196 (Box 14, Folder 74)
    - Wildmon-article in Art in America, "War on Culture", undated; 150195 (Box 14, Folder 75)
    - Wildmon-article in NY Times Magazine, "Reverend Wildmon's ..." (Sept. 2, 1990), 150194 (Box 14, Folder 76)
    - Wildmon case, undated; 150193 (Box 15, Folder 77)
    - Wildmon case-envelope and phone log, undated; 150192 (Box 15, Folder 78)
    - Wildmon-complaint/nature of claim, undated; 150191 (Box 15, Folder 79)
    - Wildmon/AFA court materials, undated; 150190 (Box 15, Folder 80)
    - Wildmon-court transcripts, undated; 150189 (Box 15, Folder 81)
    - Wildmon-flyer denouncing Wojnarowicz, undated; 150188 (Box 15, Folder 82)
    - Wildmon-law memo draft (2 versions), undated; 150187 (Box 15, Folder 83)
    - legal letter to Wildmon, undated; 150186 (Box 15, Folder 84)
    - Wildmon-legal brief notes, undated; 150185 (Box 15, Folder 85)
    - Wildmon-legal briefing notes (final version), undated; 150184 (Box 15, Folder 86)
    - Wildmon-memorandum of law, undated; 150183 (Box 15, Folder 87)
    - Wildmon-misc. flyers and memo, undated; 150182 (Box 15, Folder 88)
    - Wildmon-notes, undated; 150181 (Box 15, Folder 89)
    - Wildmon-notes, undated; 150180 (Box 15, Folder 90)
    - notes on Wildmon mailing, undated; 150179 (Box 15, Folder 91)
    - notes on Wildmon mailing, undated; 150178 (Box 15, Folder 92)
    - Wildmon-notice of appeal, undated; 150177 (Box 15, Folder 93)
    - Wildmon-People for the American Way, undated; 150176 (Box 15, Folder 94)
    - Wildmon-plaintiff's trial memo, undated; 150175 (Box 15, Folder 95)
    - Wildmon-post-trial brief, undated; 150174 (Box 15, Folder 96)
    - Wildmon-post-trial brief on libel, undated; 150173 (Box 15, Folder 97)
    - Wildmon-post-trial memo, undated; 150172 (Box 15, Folder 98)
    - Wildmon-practice cross-examination for Wojnarowicz, undated; 150171 (Box 15, Folder 99)
    - Wildmon-request for documents, undated; 150170 (Box 15, Folder 100)
    - Wildmon-trial memo, undated; 150169 (Box 15, Folder 101)
    - Wildmon-Wojnarowicz's affidavit, undated; 150168 (Box 15, Folder 102)
    - Wildmon-Wojnarowicz's affidavit, undated; 150167 (Box 15, Folder 103)
    - Wildmon-Wojnarowicz's deposition, undated; 150166 (Box 15, Folder 104)
    - Wildmon-AFA check for $1. 0, undated; 150165 (Box 15, Folder 105)
  - Subseries C: Announcements, 150138
    - Activist/political flyers, undated; 150163 (Box 15, Folder 106)
    - Announcements, undated; 150162 (Box 15, Folder 107)
    - Announcements, undated; 150161 (Box 15, Folder 108)
    - Announcements, undated; 150160 (Box 15, Folder 109)
    - Announcements, undated; 150159 (Box 15, Folder 110)
    - Announcements, undated; 150158 (Box 15, Folder 111)
    - Announcements, undated; 150157 (Box 15, Folder 112)
    - Announcements, undated; 150156 (Box 15, Folder 113)
    - Announcements, undated; 150155 (Box 15, Folder 114)
    - Announcements, undated; 150154 (Box 15, Folder 115)
    - Announcements, undated; 150153 (Box 15, Folder 116)
    - Announcements, undated; 150152 (Box 15, Folder 117)
    - Announcements - Art in America June, 1994, 150151 (Box 15, Folder 118)
    - Announcements - Art in America February, 1989, 150150 (Box 15, Folder 119)
    - Announcements - Flyer for '3 Teens Kill 4', undated; 150149 (Box 15, Folder 120)
    - '3 Teens Kill 4' Flyers/Posters, undated; 150148 (Box 15, Folder 120A.)
    - The Poetry Project, undated; 150147 (Box 15, Folder 120B.)
    - Program - Brighton Festival, undated; 150146 (Box 15, Folder 121)
  - Subseries D: General Subjects, 150124
    - Cooper, Dennis, undated; 150137 (Box 15, Folder 122)
    - Exit Art-Mailing List, undated; 150136 (Box 15, Folder 122A.)
    - Festival of Arts Cruise, undated; 150135 (Box 15, Folder 123)
    - L'Ecuyer, Gerald, undated; 150134 (Box 15, Folder 124)
    - PPOW-Announcements, undated; 150133 (Box 15, Folder 125)
    - PPOW-Bio and CV, undated; 150132 (Box 15, Folder 126)
    - PPOW-Business, undated; 150131 (Box 15, Folder 127)
    - PPOW-Reviews, undated; 150130 (Box 15, Folder 128)
    - Production Materials-Brush Fires in the Social Landscape, undated; 150129 (Box 15, Folder 129)
    - Rauffenbart, Tom-instructions for medication, undated; 150128 (Box 15, Folder 130)
    - Rauffenbart, Tom-medical card, undated; 150127 (Box 15, Folder 131)
    - Rauffenbart, Tom-rPsumP, undated; 150126 (Box 15, Folder 132)
    - Target City Hall materials --- Aids activism, undated; 150125 (Box 15, Folder 132A.)
- Series VIII: Audio [See also Accretions 2001], 149974
  Scope and Content
  Series VIII contains both complete audio works and audio source materials.
  Subseries A: Access Copies is open to researchers. For all other material please consult a Fales Archivist. Appointments are necessary for the use of manuscript and archival collections.
  - Subseries A: Access Copies, 214687
    Contains access copies for original material found in Series VIII: Subseries B, C, D, and E
    - Mexico Soundtrack, Unknown; ID: 092.0463; 214688 (Case 092.0463)
      Content description: Audio recording believed to correspond with Super 8mm film "A Fire in My Belly, a Work in Progress"
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirement note
      Format: CD
      Duration: 00:30:17
      Original Format: 1/4" audiocassette
      Source: 092.0361
    - 1988 Journal, Wojnarowicz, Nov., Dec. #1 (Part 1 of 2), ID: 092.0465; 216786 (Case 092.0465)
      Content description: Wojnarowicz talks about living at the deceased Peter Hujar's apartment, his feelings regarding his own mortality, and frustrations with the art world among other things.
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
      Duration: 00:47:08
      Source: 092.0218
    - 1988 Journal, Wojnarowicz, Nov., Dec. #1 (Part 2 of 2), ID: 092.0467; 216787 (Case 092.0467)
      Content description: Wojnarowicz speaks about his dreams, promiscuity, and fears about dying of AIDS among other things.
      Duration: 00:47:05
    - ACT UP Demonstration, June 1989, ID: 092.0469; 216788 (Case 092.0469)
      Content description: Wojnarowicz records the ACT-UP demonstrations on June 1989.
      Duration: 00:13:27
      Source: 092.0219
    - "Affair" Tape Journal 3 / 1981 (Side 1 and 2), March 1981; ID: 092.0471; 216789 (Case 092.0471)
      Content description:
      [1]-- Wojnarowicz speaks about the social difficulties he has relating to dating among other things.
      [2]--Wojnarowicz speaks about his creative process, self-doubt, and negative art critiques among other things.
      Duration:[1]--00:30:59 [2]--00:28:29
      Source: 090.0220
    - AIDS Vaccines / Gary Null Show / WBAI-5/18/90, NYC (Part 1 of 2), May 18th, 1990; ID: 092.0473; 216790 (Case 092.0473)
      Content description: Recording of the Gary Null Snow on WBAI-5/18/1990. The show's topic is about AIDS vaccines.
      Duration: 00:42:36
      Source: 092.0221
    - AIDS Vaccines / Gary Null Show / WBAI - 5/18/90, NYC (Part 2 of 2), May 18th, 1990; ID: 092.0475; 216791 (Case 092.0475)
      Content description: Part 2 of a recording Wojnarowicz made of the Gary Null Snow on WBAI-5/18/1990. The show's topic is about AIDS vaccines.
      Duration: 00:46:23
    - American Dreamtime: NYC, 1984, ID: 092.0477; 216792 (Case 092.0477)
      Content description: Experimental recording by Wojnarowicz and Doug Bressler, called "American Dreamtime." New York City, 1984.
      Duration: 00:05:37
      Source: 092.0222
    - Cross Country / Great Dreams- 1989, ID: 092.0479; 216793 (Case 092.0479)
      [1]--Wojnarowicz's audio recordings, "Cross County/Great Dreams" documents a road trip he took in 1989. He talks about his feelings regarding the death of Peter Hujar among other things.
      [2]--Wojnarowicz continues this recording in Arkansas. He talks about a dream he had and observations he's made while driving among other things.
      Duration: [1]--00:15:12 [2]--00:29:16
      Source: 092.0224
    - Cross Country / Great Dreams- 1989, ID: 092.0481; 216794 (Case 092.0481)
      [1]-- Wojnarowicz continues this series, "Cross Country/Great Dreams" in Alboroque, New Mexico. He talks about a dream he had of Peter Hujar among other things.
      [2]--Wojnarowicz is now driving towards San Diego, California. He makes general observations about the places he's traveling through and records a visit he took to the park, Sea World.
      Duration: [1]--00:31:12 [2]--00:30:53
      Source: 092.0225
    - Cross Country / Great Dreams- 1989, ID: 092.0483; 216795 (Case 092.0483)
      [1]--Wojnarowicz continues his "Cross Country/Great Dreams" recordings on February 27th. He talks about his fears of dying and observations about New York City as compared to other US cities among other things.
      [2]--Wojnarowicz documents his thoughts on the restrictions of living with AIDS coupled with his human desires among other things.
      Duration: [1]--00:30:52 [2]--00:30:04
      Source: 092.0226